<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Altro on CanzoniereOnline.it</title>
    <link>https://canzoniereonline.it/famiglia/altro/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Altro on CanzoniereOnline.it</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>it-it</language><atom:link href="https://canzoniereonline.it/famiglia/altro/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bohemien</title>
      <link>https://canzoniereonline.it/canzoni/bohemien/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://canzoniereonline.it/canzoni/bohemien/</guid>
      <description>La pioggia scende sopra i rider di Deliveroo Torno da te seguendo il profumo di ragù Milano è un gran bel ideale da inseguire Un sogno che fa solo chi non riesce mai a dormire Novembre mi ha soffiato il freddo nelle ossa La nostra foto più carina è quella mossa Mi hai detto &amp;ldquo;Guarda, sembra quella di Bandot&amp;rdquo; A me pare di no ma vabbè, già lo so che Vuoi averla sempre vinta tu, eh sì</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Genius</title>
      <link>https://canzoniereonline.it/canzoni/genius/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://canzoniereonline.it/canzoni/genius/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Labrinth&amp;rdquo; Do you think I&amp;rsquo;m stupid? Do you think I&amp;rsquo;m bat shit crazy, having you on my mind Do you think I&amp;rsquo;m helpless? My algebra gon&#39; equal you every time Do you think I&amp;rsquo;m calling? Do you think I&amp;rsquo;m calling out your name every night Girl I&amp;rsquo;ve fallen for you What, what you say?
Oh my god, baby baby don&amp;rsquo;t you see I got everything you need Only a genius will love a woman like she Oh my god, baby baby don&amp;rsquo;t you see I got everything you need Only a genius will love a woman like she</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greta Thumberg (Lo Stomaco)</title>
      <link>https://canzoniereonline.it/canzoni/greta_thumberg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://canzoniereonline.it/canzoni/greta_thumberg/</guid>
      <description>Right here, right now Right here, right—now
Sono un animalista, animalier, Animal House Dormo sotto alle stelle tipo scout Si è estinto il koala prima che io ne assaggiassi uno Tu ti estinguerai prima di aver estinto il mutuo, ehi Dall&amp;rsquo;ultima festa in un bunker, ehi Chiamo tutti pure Greta Thunberg (right now), ehi Dal tramonto di questo sistema, ehi Fino all&amp;rsquo;alba di una nuova era Ho idea che per l&amp;rsquo;inquinamento fare la differenziata Non sia abbastanza, tentano (right here) È come se per l&amp;rsquo;invecchiamento bevi la centrifugata Con l&amp;rsquo;avocado e zenzero (right now) Mi spiace che invece che al buco nell&amp;rsquo;ozono Pensavo a campare, che avevo i buchi in zona (right here) Distruggo il mio ambiente, bro, come i Rapa Nui (right now) Sono un incosciente, quindi da&#39; retta a lui, ehi</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Imagine</title>
      <link>https://canzoniereonline.it/canzoni/imagine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://canzoniereonline.it/canzoni/imagine/</guid>
      <description>Imagine there&amp;rsquo;s \C7+no heaven, it&amp;rsquo;s easy if \C7+you try. No hell \C7+below us, above us \C7+only sky. Imagine all the people living for today! A-ah-a-a-a!
Imagine there&amp;rsquo;s no countries, it isn&amp;rsquo;t hard to do. Nothing to kill or die for and no religion too. Imagine all the people living life in peace! Yu-huh-uh-uh-hu!
You may say I&amp;rsquo;m a dreamer but I&amp;rsquo;m not the only one.
I hope someday you&amp;rsquo;ll join us and the world will be as one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Memories</title>
      <link>https://canzoniereonline.it/canzoni/memories/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://canzoniereonline.it/canzoni/memories/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s to the ones that we got Cheers to the wish you were here, but you&amp;rsquo;re not &amp;lsquo;Cause the drinks bring back all the memories of everything we&amp;rsquo;ve been through Toast to the ones here today Toast to the ones that we lost on the way &amp;lsquo;Cause the drinks bring back all the memories And the memories bring back memories, bring back you
There&amp;rsquo;s a time that I remember, when I did not know no pain When I believed in forever, and everything would stay the same Now my heart feel like December, when somebody say your name &amp;lsquo;Cause I can&amp;rsquo;t reach out to call you, but I know I will one day, ay</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pastello bianco</title>
      <link>https://canzoniereonline.it/canzoni/pastello_bianco/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://canzoniereonline.it/canzoni/pastello_bianco/</guid>
      <description>E se m&amp;rsquo;hai visto piangere Sappi che era un&amp;rsquo;illusione ottica Stavo solo togliendo il mare dai miei occhi Perché ogni tanto per andare avanti sai, avanti sai Bisogna lasciar perdere i vecchi ricordi Mi chiedi come sto e non te lo dirò Il nostro vecchio gioco era di non parlare mai Come due serial killer interrogati all&amp;rsquo;FBI I tuoi segreti poi a chi li racconterai Tu che rimani sempre la mia password del wi-fi E chi sa se lo sai</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When it&#39;s time</title>
      <link>https://canzoniereonline.it/canzoni/when_its_time/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://canzoniereonline.it/canzoni/when_its_time/</guid>
      <description>Words get trapped in my mind, sorry I don&amp;rsquo;t take the time to feel the way I do. &amp;lsquo;cause the first day you came into my life, all time ticks around you
But when I need your voice and the key to unlock all the love trapped in me so tell me when it&amp;rsquo;s time to say I love you.
All I want is you to understand, that when I take your hand, it&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;cause I want to.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
