<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Abba on CanzoniereOnline.it</title>
    <link>https://canzoniereonline.it/autori/abba/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Abba on CanzoniereOnline.it</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>it-it</language><atom:link href="https://canzoniereonline.it/autori/abba/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dancing queen</title>
      <link>https://canzoniereonline.it/canzoni/dancing_queen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://canzoniereonline.it/canzoni/dancing_queen/</guid>
      <description>You can dance, you can jive, having the time of your life See that girl, watch that scene, digging the dancing queen
Friday night and the lights are low Looking out for the place to go Where they play the right music, getting in the swing You come in to look for a king
Anybody could be that guy Night is young and the music&amp;rsquo;s high With a bit of rock music, everything is fine You&amp;rsquo;re in the mood for a dance</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Does your mother know</title>
      <link>https://canzoniereonline.it/canzoni/does_your_mother_know/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://canzoniereonline.it/canzoni/does_your_mother_know/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;re so hot, teasing me So you&amp;rsquo;re blue but I can&amp;rsquo;t take a chance on a chick like you That&amp;rsquo;s something I couldn&amp;rsquo;t do There&amp;rsquo;s that look in your eyes I can read in your face that your feelings are driving you wild Ah, but girl you&amp;rsquo;re only a child
Well I can dance with you honey If you think it&amp;rsquo;s funny Does your mother know that you&amp;rsquo;re out? And I can chat with you baby Flirt a little maybe Does your mother know that you&amp;rsquo;re out?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mamma mia</title>
      <link>https://canzoniereonline.it/canzoni/mamma_mia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://canzoniereonline.it/canzoni/mamma_mia/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been cheated by you since I don&amp;rsquo;t know when So I made up my mind, it must come to an end Look at me now, \D+5will I ever learn? I don&amp;rsquo;t know how but I suddenly lose control There&amp;rsquo;s a fire within my soul
Just one look and I can hear a bell ring One more look and I forget everything, o-o-o-oh Mamma mia, here I go again My my, how can I resist you?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slipping through my fingers</title>
      <link>https://canzoniereonline.it/canzoni/slipping_through_my_fingers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://canzoniereonline.it/canzoni/slipping_through_my_fingers/</guid>
      <description>Schoolbag in hand She leaves home in the early morning Waving goodbye With an absent-minded smile I watch her go With a surge of that well-known sadness And I have to sit down for a while
The feeling that I&amp;rsquo;m losing her forever And without really entering her world I&amp;rsquo;m glad whenever I can share her laughter, that funny little girl
Slipping through my fingers all the time I try to capture every minute The feeling in it Slipping through my fingers all the time Do I really see what&amp;rsquo;s in her mind Each time I think I&amp;rsquo;m close to knowing She keeps on growing Slipping through my fingers all the time</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
